{
    "questions": [
        {
            "answer": "b",
            "options": [
                "Opera House",
                "Ferry",
                "Sunset",
                "Pagoda"
            ],
            "question": "What is a common way to travel around a city and explore famous places?",
            "type": "multiple_choice"
        },
        {
            "answer": "b",
            "options": [
                "Bridge",
                "Opera House",
                "Square",
                "Water park"
            ],
            "question": "Which place is known for performances and concerts?",
            "type": "multiple_choice"
        },
        {
            "answer": "a",
            "options": [
                "Museum",
                "Pagoda",
                "Ferry",
                "Bridge"
            ],
            "question": "What is a public place where people can see historical artifacts?",
            "type": "multiple_choice"
        },
        {
            "answer": "c",
            "options": [
                "Water park",
                "Opera House",
                "Pagoda",
                "Sunset"
            ],
            "question": "Where do people go to pray in a Buddhist culture?",
            "type": "multiple_choice"
        },
        {
            "answer": "c",
            "options": [
                "Bridge",
                "Hop-on hop-off bus",
                "Ferry",
                "Square"
            ],
            "question": "What can you use to travel across a river without a car?",
            "type": "multiple_choice"
        },
        {
            "answer": "bridge",
            "question": "A ... is a structure built over a river or road that allows people and vehicles to cross.",
            "type": "short_answer"
        },
        {
            "answer": "museum",
            "question": "People can visit a ... to learn about history and art.",
            "type": "short_answer"
        },
        {
            "answer": "Opera House",
            "question": "The Sydney ... is one of the most famous landmarks in Australia.",
            "type": "short_answer"
        },
        {
            "answer": "hop-on hop-off bus",
            "question": "If you want to travel conveniently around a city and hop on and off at different tourist attractions, you should take a ....",
            "type": "short_answer"
        },
        {
            "answer": "sunset",
            "question": "Watching the ... at the beach is a wonderful experience in the evening.",
            "type": "short_answer"
        }
    ]
}